AYAZ AHMAD

HOUSE NO#25 STREET NO#12 HAQ STREET URDU BAZAR LAHORE,PAKISTAN,PUNJAB 54000 +923227160695 1 AYAZ38PK1@OUTLOOK.COM

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Energetic, accomplished professional with more than 4 year of Administrative and accounting experience. I am well versed in administration related aspect of accounts, finance with team management Skills. Seeking a Finance & Accounts, Administration, Logistics, Customer Service or Human Resources related position where my professional experience and education will allow me to make an immediate contribution as an integral part of a progressive company.

SPECIAL SKILLS

- Experience in payroll and invoicing
- Account reconciliation expert
- Account receivable and payable expert
- Invoice and payment transaction
- Maintain accounts independently

- Excellent administrative skills
- Reporting and document preparation
- Team management and leadership
- Creativity in office work
- Customer service Skills

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

Computer: Spreadsheet, Data base Management, Windows Installation, Typing speed 75wpm

Ms office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint,

Computerized: Accounting Software, Data Entries, Internet browning, Accounting Reasearch

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Accountant Cum Admin officer

Dar-e- Argam Schools-LAHORE, PAKISTAN

Inclusive Dates: 01 May. 2015 until présent time

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- Filling of all Documents (Payments vouchers, Receipt Vouchers, Cheque Deposit Slips etc...)
- Maintain integrity of journal ledger include the chat of account
- Issue of Invoice/voucher to children at the end of every month
- Prepared daily account report and reconcile with accounting Software (Bank reconciliation statement)
- Reviewed collection reports to determine the status of collection and the amount of outstanding balance
- Collect and report monthly expense variances and explanation.
- Monthly Salary Statement of all employees' staff.
- Filling of tax return
- Arranging Annual Audit.
- Evaluate business process for effectiveness and efficiency and provide recommendation for improvement
- Ensuring that information is accurately collated & entered into systems.
- Maintain Stock register + all ledger and cash book
- Maintenance of student and employees service record

- Arrange all the meeting and event inside or outside of the school
- Ordered of all office supplies include stationary.
- Prepare and maintain all the file and register in the office
- Keep update record
- Dealing with the parents on all the issue regarding school matter and children Keep update record of student
- Maintenance of school building and daily round of the school building
- Will insure the proper distribution of work among the staff
- Any other duties assign by the management and director

Assistant Accountant.

Inclusive Dates: Sep 2012 – Mar, 2013

Faroog Brother Copy House (Publisher)-LAHORE PAKISTAN

JOB DESCRIPTION:

- Trial Balances (ledgers Balances)
- Income statement, balance sheet, cash flow.
- Keeping accounts of customer accounts (Debtors)
- Keeping accounts of suppliers (vender) accounts (Creditor)
- Issue of invoices against sales
- Daily collection and deposited into the bank.
- Business Management ideas about the new product.
- Market knowledge for purchasing the desire material.
- Update about the market material prices.
- Administrative issues.
- Closing month balances.
- Maintain company business sheets.

Lecturer ship Pakistan

- As a part time Accounting lecturer in Ali Science Academy Lahore.
- As a part time Home tuitions Crescent School, Cathedral School, Saint Peter School, Educator's School in Level from1st class to 8th Class as well as commerce subjects in level from I.com to MBA.

EDUCATION

Master of science Specialization in Accounting and Finance

The University of Lahore Pakistan

2013 to 2015

Bachelor of commerce (IT)

University of Punjab

2010 to 2012

AWARD AND ACHIEVEMENT

- Secured first position in B.com
- Participated in many Sports both during School and College Life
- Get certificate in foundation course from peak Solution College.
- Best Amin Award

REFERENCE

Available upon request